textbooksrus.com 2018-06-07

# Privacy Policy - TextbookRush

Last updated December 14, 2016

This privacy policy applies to https://www.textbookrush.com/ owned and operated by TexbookRush (collectively referred as “TexbookRush” , “we”, “us”, “our”) . This privacy policy describes how TexbookRush collects and uses the personal information you provide on our web site: https://www.textbookrush.com/ . It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information. 

When visiting any website, we encourage you to read that website's privacy policy. TextbookRush is committed to keeping your information private and confidential.

Should you have any suggestions or comments regarding our privacy policy, we encourage you to [contact us](mailto:help@textbookrush.com) or live chat with our Customer Care Department. Our complete contact information, including telephone number and physical mailing address, may be found on our contact page.

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>.

## Information Collection and Use

TextbookRush is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to any outside parties, except as outlined in this policy. TextbookRush collects information from users at several different places on our website in order to process orders and better serve you with pertinent information. Information collected includes name, shipping address, billing address, telephone numbers, e-mail address, and payment information such as credit card. TextbookRush also requires you to submit a user name and password of your choice for future access to your information. Your user name and password is to remain confidential and you should not share this information with anyone.

## Registration

In order to process your orders using this website, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give their contact information, which includes name, e-mail, telephone number and physical address. This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site, such as sending automated order status updates. **This information is NOT shared.**

## Orders

Most of the information collected in the registration process will be used to process orders. In the order process, a user must provide additional financial information such as credit card number and expiration date. This information is used for billing purposes and to fulfill customer’s orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user. We do not share your personal and financial information with any third parties. The only exception is when processing your credit card information with the merchant bank for authorization and approval. This process is protected by an enhanced security system. **Note: For enhanced security and privacy, TextbookRush does NOT save your credit/debit card information.** See Security section for more details on security measures and procedures.

## Tracking Technologies

We at TextbookRush and our marketing partners, affiliates, or analytics or service providers, use technologies such as cookies, beacons, tags, and scripts, to analyze trends, administer the website, tracking users’ movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual and aggregated basis.

We use cookies for our shopping carts, for authentication, and to customize page content. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our website, but your ability to use some features or areas of our website may be limited.

We and third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity use LSOs such as HTML 5 to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5 LSOs.

We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our website or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this website and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking [here](https://preferences.truste.com/) (or if located in the European Union click [here](https://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)). Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads.

## Log Files

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data.

We do not link this automatically collected data to other information we collect about you.

## Data Sharing

We use outside shipping companies (FedEx and USPS) to ship orders and credit card processing companies (VeriSign/Penn Securities) to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store, or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. We also use third party service providers for the shopping cart (Google Checkout & PayPal) and they do not retain, share, store, or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.

TextbookRush is located in Ohio and abides by all federal and state laws. TextbookRush will disclose any personally identifiable information when required to by law, in response to lawful requests by public authorities, such as to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, subpoena, or similar legal process when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request, but not under any other circumstances.

We may also disclose your personal information if TextbookRush is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personally identifiable information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personally identifiable information. 

## Outside Links

This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware TextbookRush is not responsible for the privacy practices of other such sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website.

## Single Sign In

You can log in to our site using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect or an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personally identifiable information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form. Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this Web site to your profile page to share with others within your network.

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button [and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site]. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. 

## Blog

Our website offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at [help@textbookrush.com](mailto:help@textbookrush.com). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

## Testimonials

We display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our website in addition to other endorsements. With your consent, we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at [help@textbookrush.com](mailto:help@textbookrush.com).

## Security

TextbookRush's website takes every precaution to protect our users’ information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, that information is protected both online and off-line. 

When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and protected with the best encryption software in the industry: SSL. Startfield Technologies, Inc uses SSL technology with advanced 128-bit encryption to process our payments. To learn more about Startfield Technologies, Inc, SSL, or payment processing, please visit [Startfield Technologies, Inc](https://www.starfieldtech.com/). 

All of our users’ information is classified and restricted. The TextbookRush facility is a secured and locked facility. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information. If you wish to have your information removed, you may contact us at [help@textbookrush.com](mailto:help@textbookrush.com) to do so. For future transactions, you will be required to re-enter your information. 

All TextbookRush servers, including web servers and database servers, are housed at TextbookRush and maintained in-house by TextbookRush. Access to the database is strictly monitored and protected from outside access. Internet access is restricted and protected by firewall and password protection. The servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment. 

We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once it is received. If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an e-mail to us at [help@textbookrush.com](mailto:help@textbookrush.com). 

## Special Offers

If you choose to receive special offers, TextbookRush may send you such pertinent information. Our special offers are sent only to customers who grant TextbookRush permission to send such information. TextbookRush does not share your information with third parties for their promotional purposes and does not solicit outside parties to send special offers on our behalf. 

Out of respect for the privacy of our users, we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Furthermore, all special offers are sent via e-mail and have a "remove link" if you wish to no longer receive special offers and news. Otherwise, customers may occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, or news. Please see our choice and opt-out below for further details of how to be removed from our mailing list. 

## Accessing/Correcting/Updating/Reviewing Personally Identifiable Information

Upon request TextbookRush will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your personal information. Customers may change or review their account information such as street address or credit card information in the My Account area, or by going to the home page and clicking on the My Account button. You MUST have your username and password in order to access your account.

If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your personally identifiable information to provide you services contact us at [help@textbookrush.com](mailto:help@textbookrush.com). We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe. We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your personally identifiable information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

## Choice/Opt-out

TextbookRush does not use customer’s information for contact other than TextbookRush pertinent business. However, for customers who wish to opt-out or be removed from TextbookRush special offers, newsletter or marketing email and related news emails, there are a couple methods to accomplish this request. Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials may opt-out of receiving these emails by using the link provided in the email to automatically unsubscribe. They may also send us an e-mail to [help@textbookrush.com](mailto:help@textbookrush.com) with a request to be removed. 

## Notification of Changes

If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users via e-mail. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. 

In the event that we make a material change to our privacy policy, we will notify you by e-mail (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or, if you have opted out of receiving any communications from TextbookRush, you may visit our website at https://www.textbookrush.com where news of changes will be posted prior to the change becoming effective. Otherwise, you may e-mail us at help@textbookrush.com. If you send us an e-mail request, we will respond to that e-mail only. You will not receive promotional materials unless you specifically grant us permission to send those. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. 

You may also send a request to our physical address at: 

TextbookRush   
802 Avondale Ave.   
Grandview Heights, OH   
43212 

#### Free shipping on orders over $35*

*A minimum purchase of $35 is required. Shipping is provided via FedEx SmartPost® and FedEx Express Saver®. Average delivery time is 1 – 5 business days, but is not guaranteed in that timeframe. Also allow 1 - 2 days for processing. Free shipping is eligible only in the continental United States and excludes Hawaii, Alaska and Puerto Rico. FedEx service marks used by permission."Marketplace" orders are not eligible for free or discounted shipping.   
Learn more about the TextbookRush Marketplace.
